<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cherchez La Film</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="chooser_title">Share</string>
    <string name="detailsEditTextHint">Share your opinion</string>

    <string name="short_description">Short film description</string>
    <string name="long_description">Long film description</string>

    <string name="coming2america_short">Coming 2 America</string>
    <string name="coming2america_long">Akeem learns he has a long-lost son in the United States and must return to America to meet the unlikely heir to the throne of Zamunda. A sequel to the 1988 comedy \'Coming to America\'.</string>
    <string name="david_kop_short">The Personal History of David Copperfield</string>
    <string name="david_kop_long">A modern take on Charles Dickens\'s classic tale of a young orphan who is able to triumph over many obstacles.</string>
    <string name="emma_short">Emma.</string>
    <string name="emma_long">In 1800s England, a well meaning but selfish young woman meddles in the love lives of her friends.</string>
    <string name="freeguy_short">Free Guy</string>
    <string name="freeguy_long">A bank teller discovers that he\'s actually an NPC inside a brutal, open world video game.</string>
    <string name="soul_short">Soul</string>
    <string name="soul_long">A musician who has lost his passion for music is transported out of his body and must find his way back with the help of an infant soul learning about herself.</string>
    <string name="topgun_short">Top Gun: Maverick</string>
    <string name="topgun_long">After more than thirty years of service as one of the Navy\'s top aviators, Pete Mitchell is where he belongs, pushing the envelope as a courageous test pilot and dodging the advancement in rank that would ground him.</string>
    <string name="kingsman_short">The King\'s Man</string>
    <string name="kingsman_long">As a collection of history\'s worst tyrants and criminal masterminds gather to plot a war to wipe out millions, one man must race against time to stop them.</string>
    <string name="tenet_short">Tenet</string>
    <string name="tenet_long">An action epic revolving around international espionage, time travel, and evolution. Possibly about a man trying to prevent World War 3 through time travel and rebirth.</string>
    <string name="french_short">The French Dispatch</string>
    <string name="french_long">A love letter to journalists set in an outpost of an American newspaper in a fictional twentieth century French city that brings to life a collection of stories published in "The French Dispatch Magazine".</string>
    <string name="bond_short">No Time to Die</string>
    <string name="bond_long">James Bond has left active service. His peace is short-lived when Felix Leiter, an old friend from the CIA, turns up asking for help, leading Bond onto the trail of a mysterious villain armed with dangerous new technology.</string>
</resources>
